uvi.net 2014-05-11

# Privacy Policy - UVI

### UVI Sounds & Software. Latest Version March 2013.

We recognize that the careful handling of your personal information is important to you. The protection of personal data is just as important to UVI. Therefore UVI commits itself to act in accordance with the following statement. With this statement you consent the collection, processing and use of your personal data by UVI for the following purposes.

1\. Personal Data

Personal data is defined as all information which allows conclusions about your personal or substantive relationships.   
Data transmitted anonymously or using a pseudonym can not be considered as personal data. 

2\. Responsible Office

Responsible party in terms of French privacy laws is: 

UVI Sounds & Software  
159 rue Amelot   
75011 Paris   
France 

3\. Use And Collection Of Data

As soon as you buy something in our shop, register a product or have yourself registered for one of our services, we need your e-mail adress, possibly your name and other personal information (i.e. postal address, telephone number, credit card information, sex, date of birth). UVI uses this data to customize your visit to our web site and to continuously improve it. 

We also use your information to communicate about orders, products, services and marketing offers with you and for updating our data sets and to maintain and update your customer accounts at UVI, to display content such as your registered products, or to display relevant updates to you, as well as recommending other products which might be interesting to you. Beyond that we use your information to improve our platform, to prevent or uncover abuse, particularly fraud or to allow third parties to exercise technical, logistic or other services on our behalf. 

4\. Information We Collect

We act according to the principle of data parsimony and data avoidance, i.e. we collect and use only the most necessary data for processing your order or product registration and for the communication with you. 

You can visit our web site without leaving personal data: When surfing without logging in we do not collect any personal data but merely place a cookie. By default information such as your IP address, time and duration of your visit, operating system, browser and visited sites are captured. 

If you register as a customer we collect your data via the registration form you fill in, among others your name, your address including e-mail, the details of your desired method of payment, your credit card number if this applies, and the details on your regarding order. Different cookies will be created in this case as well (refer to chapter 5 for details on the cookies). 

We store your order data within the ordering history and send the order data to you via e-mail. The terms and conditions can be found here. 

When registering a product via the web site, data about the registered product and the used serial number is stored. On initial registration your e-mail address and your postal address and your preferred language are stored as well. 

We also sporadically send out surveys on specific questions regarding UVI and its products. If you take part in these campaigns, your e-mail address and your answers will be stored. 

Finally, we need information on your person, at least your e-mail address in the following cases:   
◆ if you register for the delivery of a newsletter or comparable promotional material. See chapter 10. for this.   
◆ if you use our support services. In this case the data you enter into the form about your hardware and software is stored and used for follow-up, i.e. if use support a further time.   
◆ if you participate in one of our competitions or other marketing campaigns.   
◆ if you get in touch with us for other reasons.

5\. What Exactly Are Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumerical identifiers, small text files we transmit to the hard disk of your computer via your web browser or other programs. They enable UVI's systems to recognize your browser and offer you different services. No security relevant or personal data will be stored. Furthermore, cookies cannot transmit viruses, spy out data on your computer or send e-mails without your notice. Also, every web server can only read cookies it has set itself. 

Using our web site without cookies being set is possible under certain conditions; a purchase in the shop unfortunately does not work without the possibility of setting cookies. 

The most browsers are set by default to accept cookies automatically. But you can disable cookies being storing or configure your browser in a way that it notifies you before storing cookies. As you can only make full use of the most of our interesting features with cookies being enabled, we recommend leaving the cookie function on. 

Furthermore we recommend completely signing off after using a computer you share with other users if this machine is configured in a way it accepts cookies. This particularly applies to computers in public spaces, such as internet cafés or libraries. In this case we highly recommend completely signing off so that no data remain recognizable for the next user. 

6\. Information Transfer To Third Parties

The careful handling of your personal information is important to us. It is by no ways our business to sell this information. We hand over information that we receive to third parties solely for the purposes described in the following: 

a. In some cases UVI is required by law to disclose information to third parties. In particular when a crime or abuse is suspected, UVI is obliged to disclose information to law enforcement authorities. This includes exchanging information with companies that inquire credit card abuse. No personal data is passed if companies want to use them commercially. 

b. We assign other service providers, partner companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include payment processing (credit card, direct debit), analysis of our databases, handling newsletters and other promotional activities as well as analysis and documentation of our site visits (see chapter 7.a Google Analytics, 7.b "interest-based advertising", 7.c Facebook). 

These service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their tasks. However, they may not use them for any other purposes. They are also obliged to treat the information in accordance with this privacy policy and the French data protection laws. For this reason, we try to assign service providers who are bound to the French data protection regulations, or at least to the European data protection rules. 

As part of a credit card and credit assessment your name and your address are passed to such a company, whereas your rights are respected in strict accordance with statutory provisions. 

c. As we continuously develop our business, it may occur that we sell or buy individual subsidiaries, business units or parts of them. In such transactions, customer information is usually transferred together with the transferred part of the company. Your data are further subject to the previously existing privacy statement. The only exception is the case that you explicitly agree to other provisions. In the unlikely event that all or substantial parts of UVI are sold, personal information will be passed on to the buyer. 

d. In all other cases, we will inform you when personal information should be disclosed to third parties, and give you the opportunity to give your consent. 

7.a Google Analytics

In the context of Chapter 6. we want to specially point out Google Analytics. UVI uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. This service uses cookies to help analyze how the site is used. 

The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. 

Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for UVI and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

If you do not want your activity on this website to be tracked, opt out using this link: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>

7.b Google's Program for "Interest-Based Advertising"

Within the scope of its marketing operations UVI uses Google’s program for “interest-based advertising”, so-called remarketing. In the process of this program a special browser cookie is stored on the user’s computer. It is used for serving the user special ads by UVI, Google or third-party services when visiting other websites. 

Users can opt out of Google's use of these cookies by visiting the [Opt out site of Google Ads](http://tools.google.cohttp//www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.htmlm/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en%20) and the Opt out site of DoubleClick. 

7.c Facebook – Social Plug-ins

UVI's website uses plug-ins of the social network Facebook ([www.facebook.com](http://www.facebook.com/)). The plug-ins are marked with a company logo of Facebook or the addition "Facebook Social Plug-in. When you access a website from us, which contains such a plug-in, a direct connection to servers through the browser of Facebook is set up. By integrating of the plug-in, Facebook receives the information that you have visited our website. As long as you are logged in to Facebook, Facebook can assign the visit to the site to your facebook account. The plug-in transmits any actions you perform via the plug-in, e.g. pressing the “Like”-Button, directly on to Facebook, and these data will be stored there. For the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of data by Facebook, and your rights and settings taken to protect your privacy, please see the respective privacy notices from Facebook. 

To prevent such a collection of data through Facebook, you must log out on Facebook before visiting our website.

8\. Security Of Your Data

a. We have developed organizational and technical measures to reliably protect the data received from you. Our employees are intensively informed and trained and commit themselves to the data confidentiality. This ensures that your data are kept confidential. We can particularly ensure that your data is protected because we provide our customer service through our own staff and not by third parties. Thereby controls and effective training are possible. 

b. To protect your personal data during transmission to our servers, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. This encrypts all information you transmit to us. 

c. When confirming an order, we reveal only the last five digits of your credit card number. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate companies while processing the order. 

d. Furthermore, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your personal information. Part of these security measures is that we occasionally may ask you to provide proof of your identity before we disclose personal information. 

e. We would like to point out that it is important to protect yourself against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. If you share your computer with others (notably for computers in public areas such as Internet cafés and libraries), you should make sure to logout after each session. 

f. Despite these actions, there is no 100% guarantee against unauthorized third parties gaining access to your data. Consequently, we have to point out that every transmission of data over the Internet is at your own risk. 

9\. External Links

In order to provide you with comprehensive information, our website contains external links to third-party websites. To the extent that these are not clearly identifiable as such, we shall point out to you that the relevant link refers to an external website. UVI has no influence on the content and design of such third-party websites. Consequently, the guarantees given under this privacy statement do naturally not apply for such other websites. 

10\. Newsletters And Surveys

You receive a newsletter by UVI if you   
◆ have subscribe to a newsletter on our website.   
◆ have registered a product of UVI.   
◆ have downloaded a demo version. 

UVI conducts survey on specific topics. Registered users of our software are asked by e-mail to participate in such surveys. 

You can always unsubscribe form receiving both newsletters and invitations to a survey by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each newsletter.

11\. Further Advice

You have the possibility to be furnished any time at no charge with information on the data stored about you and on their use. Please describe your wishes or other questions on privacy via e-mail ([info@uvi.net](mailto:info@uvi.net?subject=UVI%20Privacy%20Policy%20Request "Contact UVI Privacy")). We will do our best to clear up your doubts. 

Any consent given to the processing of data may be revoked at any time and without stating any reasons.
